[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the four actors listed below, which one has not appeared in another movie written or directed by the Coen Brothers as of 2007?", "correct_answer": "Jeff Bridges", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Buscemi", "John Turturro", "Peter Stormare"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film written and directed by Preston Sturgess deals with a director of escapist films, who goes looking for escape.", "correct_answer": "Sullivans Travels", "incorrect_answers": ["My Travels with Charley", "The Day of the Locusts", "A Place in the Sun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the What About Bob movie, Bob marries Lily, (Dr. Marvins sister) and then becomes a psychologist himself, writing a book called Death Therapy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Earths atmosphere is about 78.8 % nitrogen and almost 21 % oxygen. This element is the third most abundant comprising about 0.93 % of the atmosphere.", "correct_answer": "Argon", "incorrect_answers": ["Helium", "Krypton", "Phosphorous"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "STOP signs have always been red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Scottish engineer was the first person to demonstrate a working television.", "correct_answer": "John Logie Baird", "incorrect_answers": ["Burr Tilstrom", "Robert Sarnoff", "Vladimir Zworykin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What alcoholic beverage is produced from herbs including the bitter herb commonly known as wormwood?", "correct_answer": "Absinthe", "incorrect_answers": ["Whiskey", "Rum", "Gin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. President settled the North Western border dispute with Canada and England?", "correct_answer": "Polk", "incorrect_answers": ["Hayes", "Mckinley", "Pierce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Pretty in Pink, Molly Ringwald played the leading lady. What was the name of her character?", "correct_answer": "Andie Walsh", "incorrect_answers": ["Andie Dong", "Andie Wash", "Amy Wells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Potato flavored ice cream can be bought in Idaho.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first spacecraft to fly by Jupiter?", "correct_answer": "Pioneer 10", "incorrect_answers": ["Voyager 1", "Pioneer 11", "Voyager 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress portrayed Jason Bournes girlfriend in The Bourne Identity?", "correct_answer": "Franke Potente", "incorrect_answers": ["Joan Allen", "Maria Helena Kreutz", "Julia Stiles"]}]